Contact +56 9 8836 3377 Anthonyjgr28@gmail.com Portfolio LinkedIn Github

PERFIL PROFESIONAL

I am a professional with experience as a Full Stack Developer and specialized training in Web Development. During my career, I have had the opportunity to lead e-commerce and IoT projects, where I have developed skills to effectively solve challenges. I consider myself a person who values teamwork and constantly seeks to improve my technical and soft skills. My main goal is to contribute significantly through innovation and commitment to excellence in every task I undertake.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senzary, Florida, USA (Remote, Startup). Full Stack Developer, August 2023 - current.

Responsibilities: Development of IoT solutions, Frontend web applications development, Backend application development, UX/UI design.

Technologies and tools: Javascript, React, Node JS, Express, nodemailer, Vercel, Github, Bitbucket, LoraWAN, Jira, Thingsboard, Thingspark, Wanesy Americas, Confluence, Trello, Excel, Slack, Discord, Figma, TeleportHQ.

Featured Projects:

-Senzary e-commerce: Played a pivotal role in the development and maintenance of the Senzary e-commerce platform. Responsible for enhancing both front-end and back-end functionalities, integrating new libraries and services to finalize the project.

Technologies: React, Redux, Tailwind, CSS, Nodemailer, Figma, Vercel, Stripe, Node JS, Express, Ups.

-Senzary web: business webpage.

Technologies: React, Figma, TeleportHQ, CSS.

-Gateways API: thingpark enterprise services are consumed to obtain a list of Gateways associated with an account, then all the sensors associated with each gateway are obtained, the relevant data is filtered and a new object is created with the required data. Afterwards, a post method is made sequentially from each Gateway with its new object and nested sensors to an application that receives them individually and is presented in a dashboard.

Technologies: Node JS, Javascript, Express, Thingsboard professional.

-loTLogIQ Data Centers Module: I studied and analyzed the internal functioning of a data room to design an IoT monitoring solution. It is currently used in 5 countries worldwide and is in a "POC" by a Fortune 500.

Technologies: Figma, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Thingsboard Professional.

Complex, Buenos Aires, Argentina. Frontend Developer, March 2023

Project contributions: landing page, 404 (3D component), loader (3D component), navbar (improve responsive), dashboard sidebar (improve responsive), footer, home styles and make the entire component responsive, review cards.

The most challenging task was achieving the design and integration of interactive and optimized 3D technology.

Technologies: React, Redux, Tailwind, CSS, Spline, 3D Max, Figma, Vercel, Mercado Pago.

My personal web portfolio . Fullstack web developer, February 2023 - current

Different projects that cover a wide range of technologies. From UI developer tools application "Color palette generator for tailwind css" to 3D web development "T-Shirt customizer". Link in the header section of this document.

Technologies: JS, HTML, CSS, Tailwind, React, Next, Three js , Spline, Figma, 3DS studio Max, Redux, Postman, Unreal engine, Mongo BD, PostgresSQL, Valtio, Express, Sequelize, Passport JS.

FrutiStore SPA . CEO - Business developer - Web designer, January 2022

E-commerce design and configuration, products database modeling, promotions and delivery methods configuration, payment methods, google analytics, instagram shopping, facebook and instagram ads.

Technologies: Jumpseller, Google analytics, Meta business manager.

Languages: Spanish and English.

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Developer | Henry Bootcamp - 2022 - 2023 First year of Bachelor's Degree in Accounting | Universidad de Margarita (UNIMAR) - 2015 - 2016 Bachelor of Theology | Instituto teológico superior Cristo Resucitado - 2011 - 2015

COMPLEMENTARY EDUCATION

Digital marketing | Udemy - 2022

Intermediate English Course full-time | Canadian College of English Language Autodidact | Protools, Logic Pro Studio, 3D Studio Max, Unity 3D, Unreal Engine, Twinmotion.